and so the format of this webinar is I
所以这次网络研讨会的格式是
will cover in the first half I'll cover
将在上半年覆盖
and the changes in improvements to your
以及对您的改进所做的更改
version control to refactoring to
版本控制重构
cogeneration the D compiler and debugger
热电联产D编译器和调试器
and some of the small changes in
还有一些小的变化
additions to the editor in the second
第二个添加到编辑器中
half of the webinar Brendan's going to
网络研讨会Brendan的一半要参加
cover some of the changes and
涵盖一些变化，
improvements to frameworks and libraries
框架和库的改进
like Android and spring and the doctor
像Android和spring以及医生
integration the first thing i want to
整合我想做的第一件事
show is some of the new changes to
显示是对的一些新更改
version control the first thing you
版本控制您的第一件事
probably noticed this the first thing
可能注意到这第一件事
that's stood out to me is an intellijel
对我来说很突出
you sir is that now there's only a
先生，您现在只有一个
single type tab which is called version
单一类型标签，称为版本
control they used to be a version
控制他们曾经是一个版本
control one and it changes one which I
控制一个，它改变一个我
found a little bit confusing now they're
发现有些困惑，现在他们
in a single tab there which you can
在一个选项卡中，您可以
click on to get to everything to do with
单击以获取与之相关的所有信息
version control so here I can see my
版本控制，所以在这里我可以看到我的
local changes and my log where I can see
本地更改和我可以查看的日志
all the commits which have gone into
所有已提交的提交
into my version control one of the
进入我的版本控制之一
things I want to talk about here is in
我想在这里谈论的事情在
this particular project I've actually
我实际上已经完成了这个特别的项目
got to VCS roots I've got one going to
扎根于VCS的根源
bitbucket I've got one going to github
我有一个去github
for reasons that are too boring to go
由于太无聊的原因
into if you click here to the to the
如果您单击此处进入
left of the commits and this out you can
提交的左边，这可以
see which commits go to which VCS routes
查看哪些提交去往哪个VCS路由
and on the paths button here if I click
并单击“路径”按钮
this I can choose to hide one of those
我可以选择隐藏其中之一
or if I had more than one and hide more
或者如果我有一个以上并隐藏更多
than one so i can select which ones are
比一个，所以我可以选择哪个
visible so this gives me a bit more
可见，所以这给了我更多
visibility over exactly what's going on
准确了解正在发生的事情
with my version control for a particular
与我的特定版本控制
project the next time I honest you I can
下次我敢说我可以
show you in this project because all the
向您展示这个项目，因为所有
commits are are in my name but if I move
提交是我的名字，但如果我搬家
to a slightly different project I can
我可以去一个稍微不同的项目
you be the highlight your own commits so
您将成为自己的亮点，因此
if i turn on highlight mike miss on here
如果我在这里打开高亮迈克小姐
you can see in a sort of yellowy color
你会看到一种淡黄色
these are all the commits that i made to
这些都是我所做的承诺
this particular project so this is quite
这个特殊的项目，所以这是相当
a good way of finding things like
找到类似东西的好方法
obviously specific commits that you made
很明显，您所做的特定提交
but also sort of seeing maybe and how
但也看到了可能以及如何
many of other people's commits have been
许多其他人的承诺是
in since the last time you commit it so
自上次提交以来
that's I think that's kind of super
我认为那是超级好
useful in a normal project that you're
在您正常的项目中很有用
collaborating on with a number of other
与其他许多人合作
developments
事态发展
in other changes for version control is
对于版本控制的其他更改是
if you remember if you've used this
如果您还记得是否曾经使用过
before you can annotate a class with the
在您可以使用
heat and with the revisions that a
热量和修订，
private of the lines of code so for
专用于代码行，因此
example I can see this line of code
例子我可以看到这行代码
change here and by me and if I scroll up
改变在这里，由我自己，如果我向上滚动
to the top and see that other changes
到顶部，然后看到其他变化
and other people in one 15.1 one of the
和其他人合而为一的15.1
changes that we made is that these
我们所做的更改是这些
changes are color coded so old changes
更改使用颜色编码，因此旧更改
are kind of red or shades of red and
是红色或红色阴影，
newer ones as we can see are in shades
我们可以看到较新的阴影
of green the ones which are kind of in
绿色的那种
between are in a sort of public kind of
之间是一种公共的
color I guess and so if I want I right
颜色，我猜是这样，如果我想要我是对的
click on one of these changes and I can
单击这些更改之一，我可以
open up this particular revision the
打开这个特定的版本
specific revision and annotate that as
具体修订并注释为
well so if I click on this then I
好吧，如果我点击这个，那么我
concede is the thing like this is the
承认是这样的事情
change i made i added this particular
我所做的更改我添加了此特定内容
method with its javadoc because it's a
其javadoc的方法，因为它是一个
good idea to javadoc public methods also
javadoc公共方法的好主意
see the state of the rest of the file
查看文件其余部分的状态
particular latent attack you might also
特殊的潜在攻击，您可能还会
have noticed that there was another
注意到还有另一个
option there which was annotate previous
在那里有注释的选项
revision now it might not be immediately
现在可能不是立即修订
obvious well that's useful for but if I
很明显，这对我很有用，但是如果我
look up here I've got two changes back
在这里查找，我有两个更改
to the back one seems to affect the
到后面似乎会影响
white space and one seems to affect the
空白，似乎会影响
methods and if I look at them there's
方法，如果我看看它们，
one that affects the white space looks
一种影响白色空间的外观
like probably it was just a formatting
可能只是一种格式
revision so I probably don't want to
修订，所以我可能不想
have a look at that because it's
看看，因为它是
probably just white space and
可能只是空白，
indentation and so forth so for this one
压痕等等，对于这个
I probably want to annotate the previous
我可能想注释上一个
revision to see the most the more
修订以查看更多
significant change that happened before
之前发生的重大变化
then so here I can see well you see that
那么在这里我可以很好地看到
white space changes and the fact that
空白空间的变化和事实
all these methods have been moved around
所有这些方法已被转移
quite a lot the last thing i want to
我想做的最后一件事
show you with the version control
向您展示版本控制
changes is there's a new mode for the
变化是有一种新的模式
diff tool so if i go sexy if i try and
差异工具，所以如果我尝试，如果我变得性感
show the diff between the changes I've
显示我所做的更改之间的差异
made tradition we have this by stiff we
成为传统，我们僵硬地拥有了
have the
有
file on the left and the new file on the
文件在左侧，新文件在
right and I have to sort of scroll
对的，我必须滚动一下
sideways what my change worth in this
在这方面我的改变值得
particular case what i did is i did a
特殊情况下我所做的是我做了一个
generic parameter fitted in such as in
通用参数，例如
many cases this is kind of useful and i
很多情况下这很有用，我
think lots of people don't mind
认为很多人不介意
side-by-side diff but there's a new
并排比较，但有一个新
viewer or we can pick the one side
查看器，或者我们可以选择一侧
viewer and here we can see the original
查看器，在这里我们可以看到原始的
line of code or certainly the previous
代码行或肯定是前一行
line of code at the top here and the new
顶部的代码行和新的
line of code directly underneath it with
直接在下面的代码行
the specific changes highlighted in a
突出显示的特定更改
kind of more green green if you like so
如果您喜欢，则更绿色
this gives us a bit more flexibility
这给了我们更多的灵活性
overs over how we see the diffs between
我们如何看待两者之间的差异
the previous version of the file and the
文件的先前版本和
new version what I'd like to do now is
我现在想做的新版本是
move on to the change within refactoring
继续进行重构中的更改
oh let this project because I'm done
哦，让这个项目，因为我完成了
with that let's open up very facturing
有了它，我们就可以开放
project so one of the things I think is
项目，所以我认为的一件事是
really cool about IntelliJ IDEA 14.1 is
IntelliJ IDEA 14.1真的很酷
that although there are some new me
尽管有一些新的我
factoring and I'll show you one of them
保理，我给你看其中之一
in a minute the existing refactorings
在一分钟内，现有的重构
that we use all the time have actually
我们一直使用的时间实际上
just got a lot smarter so for example
变得更聪明了，例如
extract method if I wanted to extract
如果我要提取的提取方法
this method in a previous version of
先前版本中的此方法
IntelliJ it would pull out that line of
IntelliJ，它将拉出那条线
code and put it into a method and that's
代码并将其放入方法中
great but what it can't what it couldn't
很棒，但是它不能做什么
do then was figure out the line above is
然后做的是找出上面的行是
actually very similar to that line but
实际上与那条线非常相似，但是
not exactly the same and just a small
不完全相同，只是很小
change in the method signature will
方法签名的变化将
allow us to reuse that let me
让我们重用那让我
demonstrate that so if I pull this out
证明这一点，如果我把它拉出来
into a method then let's call this print
进入一个方法，然后我们称之为打印
in the new version of and let's make
在新版本中，让
this a bit bigger so we can see it
这个更大一点，我们可以看到它
better what intelligence suggests me is
更好的情报表明我是
maybe you fast this string in as a
也许你把这个字符串作为一个
parameter then maybe I'll be able to
参数，那么也许我将能够
replace more instances of of code with
用替换更多的代码实例
this new method so I'm going to accept
这种新方法，所以我要接受
that signature change I'm going to
我将要进行的签名更改
replace this one at the top as well so
最好也替换在顶部
it's found another place where I can use
找到了另一个我可以使用的地方
that method so let's replace that I
该方法，让我们替换掉我
don't know if you can see but right at
不知道你是否能看到，但是就在
the bottom of my screen
屏幕底部
showing which shortcuts i'm using for
显示我正在使用的快捷方式
for doing things like extract method i'm
做类似提取方法的事情
on windows so i'm using windows ones but
在Windows上，所以我正在使用Windows的，但
at the bottom it will show you the
在底部，它将向您显示
windows and the map bindings as well the
Windows和地图绑定以及
windows ones are usually very similar to
Windows的通常非常类似于
the Linux ones so I'm not ignoring the
Linux的，所以我不会忽略
Linux guys and so also another extract
Linux专家等也摘录
method change is if we want to extract
方法更改是如果我们要提取
this one here I have a method and
我这里有一个方法
instance method and here I have a static
实例方法，这里我有一个静态
method if I extract this I success on
方法，如果我提取这个我成功
the strike method again let's call it
再次使用罢工方法
print it offers me the same again it
打印它再次为我提供相同的东西
wants me to pull this out into a printer
要我把它拉进打印机
so that's fine that's the same thing
所以没关系
I've just demonstrated and it's up that
我刚刚演示了
I can replace this one with the new
我可以用新的代替
method call but it needs to turn it into
方法调用，但需要将其转换为
a static method if it does that so if i
静态方法，如果这样做的话，如果我
replace there perhaps it figures out
替换那里也许它弄清楚了
this new method needs to be a static
这个新方法必须是静态的
method but that's okay because it
方法，但是没关系，因为它
doesn't really impact either of these
并没有真正影响这些
two places that call that method so with
调用该方法的两个地方
the extract method intellij idea is just
提取方法intellij的想法只是
being a little bit smarter about some of
在某些方面变得更聪明
the places where there might be
可能有的地方
duplicates lightly different shape could
略有不同的形状可以复制
use these methods that we've district
使用我们已经分区的这些方法
we've extracted but it's not just
我们已经提取了，但不仅仅是
extracting methods that's been changed
提取已更改的方法
it's so and call hierarchy is but so if
是这样，呼叫层次结构是，但是如果
for example if we change the shape of
例如，如果我们改变形状
the of the method if we change the
如果我们更改方法的
method parameters we can also figure out
方法参数我们也可以找出
some smarter things to do so i'm going
我要做一些更聪明的事情
to add a parameter to this method here
在此处向此方法添加参数
what we've got is method called fuj cos
我们所拥有的是称为fu cos的方法
bar method called bar which calls bars
bar方法称为bar，它调用bar
and a method called bears which does
还有一种叫做Bears的方法
nothing but obviously this is a
没什么，但显然这是一个
massively over simplified example but
大大超过简化的例子，但
imagine if you had a multi-tiered
想象一下，如果您有一个多层
architecture it's not unusual to find a
架构，找到一个并不少见
call hierarchy where say a method in
调用层次结构，其中说一个方法
your service layer cause method in your
您的服务层原因方法
dao layer which caused another method
道层导致另一种方法
somewhere else and and so you might have
其他地方，所以你可能有
a stack of method calls throughout your
整个您的方法调用堆栈
hierarchy now let's say you want to add
现在假设您要添加层次结构
a parameter to this fast method I'm
我是这种快速方法的参数
going to add an interpreter
要添加翻译
and call it I because I'm not going to
叫我，因为我不会
call it integer because it's a good idea
称它为整数，因为这是一个好主意
to call methods for call parameters
调用方法作为调用参数
something useful that's fine and
有用的东西很好
apparently there's a feature an
显然有一个功能
underused feature in intellij which has
intellij中未充分使用的功能
been around for a while which is this
已经有一段时间了，这是
propagate parameters feature so if I
传播参数功能，如果我
heard that it's me the option to
听说这是我的选择
propagate this parameter from bears all
从所有传播此参数
the way up through bar and through food
通过酒吧和食物的方式
so if I select foo it will add that
因此，如果我选择foo，它将添加
parameter to all of those methods since
因为所有这些方法的参数
its death I'm going to refactor this
它的死亡，我要重构这个
test and now you can see I've got this
测试，现在您可以看到我已经有了
integer parameter on on all of my
我所有的整数参数
methods so that's fine apparently that's
方法，这很好，显然是
been around for a little while it's not
已经有一段时间了
something I was aware of one of the
我知道的其中一项
changes that's coming in 14.1 though is
14.1中即将进行的更改是
if I want for example to now delete this
如果我想例如现在删除此
parameter because unused I'm going to
参数，因为我将不使用
delete it without delete IntelliJ IDEA
删除而不删除IntelliJ IDEA
detects that it can also delete it from
检测到它也可以从中删除它
the call hierarchy as well so I can
以及呼叫层次结构
click foo and it be removed from all of
单击foo，然后将其从所有
those methods great the same thing works
这些方法同样有效
if I want to make this method static so
如果我想使此方法静态
refactor make it static we factor there
重构使其静态，我们在那里分解
and IntelliJ asks me if I want to make
IntelliJ问我是否要
all of those methods static which I do
我做的所有那些静态方法
and then finally this method foo is not
然后最后这个方法foo不是
being used not surprisingly because it's
被使用并不奇怪，因为它是
an example but let's say our top level
一个例子，但让我们说我们的顶级
method isn't being used anymore we want
我们不再想要使用该方法
to delete them then IntelliJ IDEA
删除它们然后IntelliJ IDEA
figures out that we can delete all of
弄清楚我们可以删除所有
those methods because they're only used
这些方法，因为它们仅被使用
in this cool hierarchy so that's some
在这个很酷的层次结构中
quite nice changes to the way
方式的相当不错的改变
refactoring works inside IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中的重构工作
we don't really need to learn that many
我们真的不需要学习那么多
new things it's just IntelliJ is going
只是IntelliJ的新事物
to suggest additional things to you when
在什么时候向你建议其他事情
you're trying to refactor things that
您正在尝试重构那些
perhaps it didn't suggest to you before
也许以前没给你建议
now and I want to show you the one of
现在，我想向您展示
the really cool things i think in
我想的很酷的东西
IntelliJ IDEA fort important need a
IntelliJ IDEA要塞很重要
different project for this because you
不同的项目，因为你
know it's all about it before RT point
在RT点之前就知道了
so i want to show you how to extract a
所以我想告诉你如何提取一个
functional parameter now we're all using
功能参数，现在我们都在使用
java 8 right
Java 8对
or thinking about Java 8 is if which
或考虑使用Java 8是
other people then we're starting to
其他人，那么我们开始
think in terms of more functional
考虑更多功能
patterns so we're not just talking about
模式，所以我们不只是在谈论
passing around objects or passing around
绕过物体或绕过
like a boolean value here or an int
就像这里的布尔值或整数
value there we might be passing around
珍惜那里，我们可能会过去
functions so we might passing around
功能，所以我们可能会过去
lambdas so intellij idea is refactoring
lambdas，所以intellij的想法正在重构
has changed to help us do this as well
已经改变以帮助我们做到这一点
so let's say we want to what I've got
所以说我们想要我所拥有的
here is I've got method which does three
这是我有做三个的方法
very similar things depending on
非常相似的东西取决于
different criteria so I'm going to do
不同的标准，所以我要去做
this so this is happy this is it's
这很高兴这是
confused now that looks kind of like a
现在很困惑，看起来像一个
right place for refactoring because i'm
重构的正确地方，因为我
repeating code so let's try and refactor
重复代码，让我们尝试重构
this let's call it increment pie so I've
我们称之为增量派，所以我已经
method increment pie let's just do some
方法增量派让我们来做一些
sort of sounded refactorings like I'm
听起来像是我的重构
going to extract this parameter well i'm
我要很好地提取此参数
going to extract this into a parameters
要将其提取为参数
as well let's call that pie slice now
我们现在也叫那个馅饼
IntelliJ works out that this code can be
IntelliJ计算出该代码可以
replaced with this method call airs on
替换为此方法，调用airs on
to fine great so we've reduced code
很好，所以我们减少了代码
duplication and pulled out a single
复制并取出一个
method that's great but what we might
很棒的方法，但是我们可能会
want to do is just go one step further
想做的就是再走一步
maybe we want to do something a little
也许我们想做点事
bit more generic than this maybe we want
比我们想要的更通用
this to be I think a do if method and we
这是我认为的“如果做方法”，我们
wanted to do some functionality based on
想做一些基于
some criteria so what I want to do is
一些标准，所以我想做的是
pull this out into a lambda now I can do
现在我可以把它拉成lambda
that with ctrl shift alt p it's a one
ctrl shift alt p是一个
extra button to press to extract the
额外的按钮可按以提取
parameter the functional parameter so
参数功能参数
I'm trying to extract this is a
我正在尝试提取这是一个
functional parameter IntelliJ IDEA
功能参数IntelliJ IDEA
suggests a number of functional
建议一些功能
interfaces which have got the right and
正确的接口和
the right signature for this particular
此特定的正确签名
call so this takes no arguments and a
调用，因此不需要任何参数，并且
returns void so it's suggesting these
返回void，因此建议这些
functional interfaces and maybe I could
功能接口，也许我可以
use runnable that's fine but maybe I
使用runnable很好，但也许我
decide that runnable is a little bit to
决定可运行有点
be generically for me so what I want is
通常对我来说，所以我想要的是
my own interface so let's have a
我自己的界面，所以让我们
interface
接口
call it in fermentable well let's give
称它为发酵罐吧
it a increment increment method we need
它是我们需要的增量增量方法
to tag this under driver 8 we need we
要在驱动程序8下标记此标签，我们需要
should take this as a functional
应该将此作为功能
interface now when I try and extract
现在，当我尝试提取时界面
this as a functional parameter it offers
这是它提供的功能参数
me incremental as a as a valid
我作为有效的增量
functional parameter so let's do that
功能参数，让我们这样做
let's close out now you'll see what
让我们现在关闭，你会看到什么
IntelliJ has done has is put this in as
IntelliJ所做的已将其作为
an anonymous in a class and that's kind
一个班上的匿名者
of fine because actually that means we
很好，因为实际上这意味着我们
can apply this evenin non Java 8 coat so
即使在非Java 8外套中也可以使用
we can use this in java 6 code if we
如果我们可以在Java 6代码中使用它
want to especially if say we're not
想要特别是如果说我们不是
using Java 8 yet but we're trying to
使用Java 8，但我们正在尝试
refactor our code to a more functional
重构我们的代码使其更具功能
style before we get there then maybe we
我们到达那里之前的风格，然后也许我们
want to remove this way man there's a
要删除这种方式的人有一个
lot of boilerplate there so if we are
有很多样板，所以如果我们
using Java 8 then what we can do is use
使用Java 8然后我们可以做的就是使用
some of intelligence inspections for
一些情报检查
helping make our code a little bit more
帮助使我们的代码多一点
succinct for example in this case I'm
例如，在这种情况下，我很简洁
going to use a method reference because
将使用方法参考，因为
I think that's kind of the shortest wire
我认为那是最短的电线
heat to represent this but you don't
热能代表这个，但你不
have to use a method reference code for
必须使用方法参考代码
example they refactor this to a lamp so
例如他们将其重构为一盏灯
I can use it either as a lambda or as a
我可以将其用作lambda或
method reference so that's IntelliJ IDEA
方法参考，所以这是IntelliJ IDEA
support for pulling out functional
支持拉出功能
parameters so that you can start passing
参数，以便您可以开始传递
bits of behavior around not just objects
不仅仅是对象周围的一些行为
I think that's a really interesting
我觉得那真的很有趣
feature here in this in the new version
在新版本中的此功能
of the IDE as well as refactorings we've
IDE以及我们进行的重构
also got some changes in code generation
在代码生成方面也有一些变化
I sort of see these two things as going
我觉得这两件事正在进行中
quite hand in hand because both of these
相当齐头并进，因为这两个
things are the ideas of taking over some
事情是接管一些的想法
of the boring stuff that you don't want
不想的无聊的东西
to do and just allowing you to get on
去做，只是让你继续
with more interesting bit of coding so
与更多有趣的编码，所以
let's take for example and equals and
让我们举个例子，等于
hashcode let me find a or let mean that
哈希码让我找到一个或让其表示
it's not work let me find some some
不行，让我找一些
things and equals an sss on I've little
事情和等于对我有点
pojo so this is a Twitter user is going
pojo，所以这是一个Twitter用户
series of properties now let's say I
现在说一系列属性
want to add an equals method on to this
想要在其上添加一个equals方法
I can use my generate equals and
我可以使用生成等于
hashcode
哈希码
normally I might use the IntelliJ
通常我可能会使用IntelliJ
default so let's have a look at that
默认，让我们看一下
let's use that intellij default let's
让我们使用intellij的默认值
make those all non 0 and IntelliJ
使所有这些都非0和IntelliJ
general x equals method now personally
现在一般x等于方法
I'm a big fan of having curly braces
我是花括号的忠实粉丝
around my lips so I kind of wanted to
在我的嘴唇周围，所以我有点想
look a bit like this but my generated
看起来有点像这样，但我产生了
code doesn't look the way I want my code
代码看起来不像我想要的代码
to look so I can change the templates
看起来，以便我可以更改模板
for my generated code so that it it
对于我生成的代码
meets my requirements so let's just back
符合我的要求，让我们回来吧
that out again so this time we're going
再次出来，所以这次我们要
to insert r equals episode we can select
插入r等于情节，我们可以选择
one of these all existing defaults or
这些所有现有默认值之一，或者
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是
create my own template I'm going to
创建我自己的模板
crazy the defaults on here we'll call it
疯狂在这里的默认值，我们称之为
a no project default and what I wanted
没有项目的默认设置，我想要什么
to do is I'm going to go ahead to one of
我要做的是继续前进
these macros this fro is the field
这些宏这是领域
comparison that it was just using to
比较，它只是用来
generate their equals method so I want
生成他们的equals方法，所以我想要
to put curly braces around my around my
把花括号放在我周围
ears now you'll notice i urge you don't
耳朵现在您会发现我敦促您不要
need to format this correctly i can
需要正确格式化这个我可以
actually just kind of put my adversities
实际上只是让我陷入困境
more or less wherever I want to and when
或多或少我想去的地方和时间
IntelliJ inserts this code it will
IntelliJ将插入此代码，它将
format the code according to your
根据您的代码格式化代码
standards so let's say I make those
标准，所以说我做那些
changes i'm going to rename this so that
改变我要重命名这个，以便
i know this is the one had changed and
我知道这是已经改变的
also to demonstrate mother feature to
还要展示母亲的特征
you so if I've got to allow this is
你，所以如果我必须允许这是
called you can see that actually
叫你可以看到
intelligence giving you some code hints
智能为您提供一些代码提示
even inside this template's box so it's
甚至在这个模板的盒子里面，所以
telling me there's no longer a macro
告诉我不再有宏
called add fields of comparison so what
叫做添加比较字段，那么
i can do is i can look for something
我能做的是我可以寻找东西
which is right so I want project field
这是正确的，所以我想要项目领域
comparison so I get my autocomplete ever
比较，这样我就可以获得自动完成功能
even inside this templates so let's see
即使在此模板内，让我们来看
I've posted this project default I've
我已将此项目发布为默认值
changed my default so it puts curly
更改了我的默认设置，使它卷曲了
braces in there so that should be
大括号在那里，应该
everything I want to do let's click
我想做的所有事情都让我们点击
through click all of these now when i
通过单击所有这些现在当我
get my native code I've got curly braces
得到我的本机代码我有花括号
in my energy equals code so this is
用我的精力等于代码，所以这是
quite a nice feature for us especially
对我们来说是一个很好的功能
if we want our code follow a particular
如果我们希望我们的代码遵循特定的
guidelines we can have the code
准则，我们可以有代码
generation follow
一代跟随
guidelines as well we don't just have to
准则，我们也不必
to put up with whatever gets inserted
忍受插入的任何东西
into our code next up I've just got two
接下来我们的代码中，我只有两个
more areas i want to show you so next up
接下来我想向您展示更多领域
I'm going to move on to the c compiler
我将继续使用C编译器
and debugging so in IntelliJ IDEA for
和调试，因此在IntelliJ IDEA中
teens bring up the test class in
青少年在参加考试班
IntelliJ IDEA 14 we had quite a lot of
IntelliJ IDEA 14我们有很多
improvements in both the debugging area
调试方面的改进
and we had this idea of the built-in
我们有内置的想法
decompiler so if I drill through to code
反编译，所以如果我钻到代码
that i don't own so for example here I
我不拥有，所以例如在这里我
haven't actually does have sources
实际上没有来源
intelligence and telling me it's quite
情报告诉我这很
small text and it's quite difficult to
小文字，很难
see but this is a decompiled classifier
看到的，但这是一个反编译的分类器
so it's making based on the based on the
所以它是基于
bytecode it's kind of giving me readable
字节码，这使我可读
code so i can understand what's going on
代码，以便我了解发生了什么
now this was available in IntelliJ 14
现在可以在IntelliJ 14中使用
but in 14.1 I can actually add my own
但在14.1中我实际上可以添加自己的
breakpoints in here and step through and
这里的断点并逐步执行
debug this as if it were almost my own
调试它，就像几乎是我自己的一样
code that I owned so it gives me a lot
我拥有的代码给我很多
more visibility even over the code that
即使在
isn't mine as I'm trying to figure out
不是我的，因为我想弄清楚
maybe a particular problem or try and
也许是一个特殊的问题或尝试
figure out exactly how something works
弄清楚到底是怎么工作的
so I'll put a breakpoint in here let's
所以我在这里放一个断点
go back to my text and if I start
回到我的文字，如果我开始
running this let's let's start debugging
运行此，让我们开始调试
it rather than running it we can see
它而不是运行它，我们可以看到
some of the we can see the debug are
我们可以看到的一些调试是
doing what it's supposed to do so I
做应该做的事
really liked the new debugging features
非常喜欢新的调试功能
in version 14 anyway I in them I think
无论如何，在版本14中，我认为
this is in 14.1 we got these these new
这是在14.1中，我们得到了这些新的
buttons as well so everything's all kind
按钮，所以一切都很好
of shiny and new and so let's step into
闪亮和新颖，让我们走进
where we're debugs here we're stepping
我们在这里调试的地方
into the decompiled class while so i can
进入反编译类，而我可以
step in and keep looking for stuff or
介入并继续寻找东西或
what I'm different I'm going to run to
我要去的不同之处
my break point and here I can see again
我的突破点，在这里我可以再次看到
my inline debugging that we got in
我进入的在线调试
IntelliJ 14 is available inside here so
IntelliJ 14在这里可用，因此
I can see the actual value was one
我可以看到实际值是一
expected value is 2 and this is the
期望值为2，这是
string description that we're going to
我们要去的字符串描述
get so I this is definitely going to
得到所以我这绝对是
fail so I can see why it's failing and
失败，所以我可以看到为什么失败了，
what the what the values were
价值是什么
so the final thing I want to look at is
所以我最后要看的是
I want to show some of the general
我想展示一些一般
changes to the overall editor so let's
更改整体编辑器，所以让我们
final projects in and a number of
的最终项目以及许多
changes which just make our lives as
变化使我们的生活成为
developers just that little bit easier
开发人员容易一点
and so for example they've changed
例如，他们已经改变了
things like the look and feel of the
诸如外观和感觉之类的东西
tabs so let's have a look at the tab
标签，让我们看看标签
here let's spell tabs quickly I'm having
在这里让我们快速拼写标签
a bad spelling day today so let's split
今天是糟糕的拼写天，让我们分开
the tabs at the top and so if I open
顶部的标签，如果我打开
another tab here they slightly change
另一个标签在这里他们略有变化
them fear love it and so that's just a
他们害怕爱它，所以那只是一个
tiny enhancement and speaking of which
微小的增强，并谈到
you can sort of see that when you've got
你可以看到，当你有
a lot of these things open you've got
这些事情很多，你有
your tabs open and you've got this
您的标签页打开，您已经拥有了
window open and you've got a bunch of
窗户打开，你有一堆
verbs around sides there's a lot of
两侧的动词有很多
stuff getting in the way getting in
东西进入的方式
between you and your actual code so one
在你和你的实际代码之间
of the new modes is as an distract so i
的新模式是分散注意力，所以我
can enter distraction free mode and that
可以进入无干扰模式
just gets rid of all that clutter and I
摆脱了所有的混乱，我
can just focus on on just my code I
我可以只专注于我的代码
still get useful information like which
仍然获得有用的信息，例如
lines of code I've changed and I have
我已更改的代码行
things like some of the errors are
像一些错误的事情是
available on the side I can still code
我仍然可以在一边编码
the way expected and speaking of which
预期的方式和说话方式
I'm going to use this mode to
我将使用此模式
demonstrate some of the new features so
展示一些新功能
in HTML it's quite easy to change whiles
在HTML中，很容易更改
and tag and forget to change the closing
并标记并忘记更改结束
tag I mean IntelliJ will at least tell
标签，我是说IntelliJ至少会告诉
you that you're missing a closing tag
您，您缺少结束标记
but it's very easy to make these sorts
但是做这些事情很容易
of simple mistakes in 14.1 you setting
您设置的14.1中的简单错误
simultaneous tag editing so if I turn
同时进行标签编辑，如果我打开
that on set that to okay now if I change
如果我改变的话，现在就可以了
this then my closing tag gets changed as
然后我的结束标签被更改为
well so i can do that here so i know
好吧，我可以在这里做，所以我知道
that my HTML is well-formed no matter
我的HTML格式正确
what changes are making to the tabs and
选项卡进行了哪些更改，以及
there's a really nice way just to stop
有一个很好的方法只是停止
us making silly mistakes which is so
我们犯了愚蠢的错误
easy to make and the left speaker that I
容易制作，我的左扬声器
want to show let's say I put two more
想展示我说再放两个
dips in here
浸在这里
now i can do i can create two curses in
现在我可以做，我可以在里面创造两个诅咒
my coat by pressing Shift + Alt and then
按Shift + Alt，然后按
selecting with the mouse and I can
用鼠标选择，我可以
select with both those curses and it can
选择那些诅咒，它可以
for example now cut with both of those
例如现在用两个
couple verses and then if I create
几节经文，如果我创造
another two cursors down here space in
下方还有两个光标
there I can paste those two different
在那里我可以粘贴这两个不同的
values into the two new positions of the
价值观进入了两个新的位置
curses I think this is really useful for
诅咒，我认为这对于
doing things like string manipulation
做诸如字符串操作之类的事情
and moving stuff around inside the code
并在代码内移动内容
and so that you can maybe neaten at your
这样你就可以整装待发
code or maybe extract parameters from
代码或从中提取参数
from concrete strengths I think that's
从具体的优势，我认为那是
all I had to cover so I've covered
我所必须涵盖的所有内容
version control I've covered the new
我已经介绍了新的版本控制
refactoring capabilities I've covered
我介绍的重构功能
code generation I've covered debugging d
我已经介绍了调试d的代码生成
compiled code and I've covered some of
编译的代码，我已经介绍了一些
the changes to the editor so we're going
对编辑器所做的更改，所以我们要
to switch over to tipton presenting his
切换到Tipton展示他的
half of the webinar and in the meantime
网络研讨会的一半，与此同时
maybe we can field some of the questions
也许我们可以提出一些问题
as well while we do the hand over that
在我们交接的时候
was great Tricia um I really like the
Tricia um很棒，我真的很喜欢
extract functional parameter I think
提取我认为的功能参数
i'll be using that protecting a lot
我会用很多保护
that's uh I think that's pretty cool I
我觉得那很酷
think that's my new favorite i think i'm
认为这是我的新宠，我认为
going to use that a lot in the future so
将来会经常使用
we have we have a bunch of questions and
我们有很多问题，
treasure will continue answer them in
宝将继续回答他们
the webinar screen and i'll switch over
网络研讨会屏幕，我将切换
to my screen now and i'll be
现在我的屏幕上，我会
demonstrating three new framework and
展示了三个新框架
technologies that you'll find in
您会发现的技术
intellij idea of 14.1 these are by no
intellij 14.1的想法不是
means comprehensive but um I think they
意味着全面，但是我认为他们
highlight some of really great features
突出一些非常好的功能
for framework support and first we'll go
获得框架支持，首先我们要去
over spring boot so there's a new
在 spring boot 上，所以有一个新的
improvements for spring boot support and
改进了对弹簧靴的支持，并
we'll talk about how you can deploy
我们将讨论如何部署
application really easily with docker
使用docker真的很容易
and finally we'll discuss some new
最后，我们将讨论一些新的
improvements to android support in the
对android支持的改进
latest version of IntelliJ IDEA so I
最新版本的IntelliJ IDEA，所以我
will hold the questions to the end and
将问题一直保留到最后
we'll get straight into it I have a new
我们会直接进入它，我有一个新的
spring boot project set up and will
春季启动项目成立，并将
quickly go over how to set a new
快速查看如何设置新的
springwood project up using the wizard
使用向导启动springwood项目
so there's now a spring boot initializer
所以现在有一个Spring Boot初始化程序
a wizard to help you get up and running
一个向导来帮助您启动和运行
with spring boots so you can configure
带有弹簧靴，因此您可以配置
all of the initialization options for
的所有初始化选项
this project if you're using a maven or
如果您使用的是Maven或
a Gradle based build will be able to
基于Gradle的构建将能够
tell it right here in the wizard and
在向导中告诉它，然后
give it a packaging option a language
给它一个包装选项的语言
and so forth and you'll need to select a
依此类推，您需要选择一个
subset of core dependencies or
核心依赖项的子集或
technology verticals that you'd like to
您想要的技术垂直领域
use inside your spring good application
在您的spring内部很好的应用程序中使用
and with spring boot does is it makes it
并用弹簧靴做到了
really easy to use the conventions in
真的很容易使用约定
spring without having to do a whole lot
春天，不必做很多事情
of configuration so whether you're using
配置，因此无论您使用
this to quickly prototype maybe a
这可以快速制作原型
back-end restful web service or stay a
后端宁静的Web服务或保持
user facing web application or something
用户面对的Web应用程序或其他东西
else you can select those dependencies
否则你可以选择那些依赖
that you'd like to import and what the
您要导入的内容以及
initializer wizard will do is it will
初始化向导会做的是
configure your maven com or Gradle build
配置您的Maven com或Gradle构建
script to use all the correct versions
使用所有正确版本的脚本
for these technologies and and set those
这些技术，并设置
up for you and so you can select the
为您服务，因此您可以选择
ones you'd like and springwood version
您想要的和springwood版本
and I think spring boot 1.3 was recently
我认为spring boot 1.3是最近的
released just this week and you can use
就在本周发布，您可以使用
all of that and it will pull down the
所有这些都会拉低
project template from from start that
从一开始的项目模板
spring that I oh and you'll be able to
春天，我哦，你将能够
use that right inside your
在您的内部使用
IED and so this is now integrated right
IED，因此现在已集成
inside IntelliJ IDEA and it helps kind
在IntelliJ IDEA中，它有助于
of quickly go from the conception of
迅速摆脱了
what technology is like to use to a
使用什么样的技术
working project in just a few simple
几个简单的工作项目
steps and this is a great feature in
步骤，这是一个很棒的功能
spring boot and now intend IntelliJ IDEA
春季启动，现在打算使用IntelliJ IDEA
as well but the support doesn't end
同样，但支持并没有结束
there you can go into your spring boot
在那里你可以进入你的 spring boot
application and you may not know this
应用程序，您可能不知道
but you can edit your property files now
但您现在可以编辑属性文件
with complete code assistance inside the
在内部提供完整的代码帮助
editor and this is really thoughtfully
编辑，这真的很周到
done I think so there's code completion
我认为完成了，所以代码完成了
for new property keys so if you don't
用于新的属性键，所以如果您不这样做
know the entire the fully qualified name
知道整个全限定名
for the key you can just type a
对于键，您只需键入一个
substring and select from the code
子字符串，然后从代码中选择
completion and there's completion in the
完成，并且在完成
value as well additionally there's
价值，还有
navigation support between these
这些之间的导航支持
property these properties and their
这些属性及其属性
associated property sources in Java so
Java中的相关属性源
these correspond to setters that you can
这些对应于您可以的二传手
specify whether it's some something
指定是否有些东西
inside the spring dependencies the start
在spring依赖中开始
of dependencies or a custom property
依赖项或自定义属性
that you can define on your own so if
你可以自己定义
there's a property that's not defined we
有一个未定义的属性
can start writing our own my custom
可以开始自己写我的习惯了
property and it automatically does the
属性，它会自动执行
validation against these keys and it
根据这些密钥进行验证
says well this property isn't available
说的很好，此属性不可用
we can define the configuration key and
我们可以定义配置密钥和
a lot about it could create that inside
关于它的很多事情可以在里面创造出来
inside this JSON the five
在此JSON中，五个
additionally you even when you deploy
另外，即使您部署
this to either your local machine
这到您的本地计算机
there's new configuration options in the
有新的配置选项
run and debug configurations so you'll
运行和调试配置，以便您将
find a new spring boot run in debug
在调试中找到新的Spring Boot运行
configuration here you'll be able to
在这里配置，您将能够
override these parameters and specify
覆盖这些参数并指定
any active profiles you're using for
您用于的任何活动配置文件
spring beans so I can override a number
春豆，所以我可以覆盖一个数字
of Crowder's inside right inside this
里面的人群的内部
run to pub configuration and again and
运行到发布配置，然后再次
there's code completion in here as well
这里也有代码完成
so we try to do is kind of remove any
所以我们尝试做的是删除任何
obstacles so that you don't have to look
障碍，所以你不必看
all these things up or muck around in
所有这些事情或混入
and XML or anything like that so that's
和XML或类似的东西，所以
very helpful so if we'd like to go ahead
非常有帮助，所以如果我们想继续
and run this which springwood does is it
并运行Springwood做的
provides built-in application server so
提供内置的应用服务器，因此
all you need to do is just run an
您需要做的就是运行一个
application and it will deploy it to a
应用程序，它将部署到
local instance of our Java or JVM and
Java或JVM的本地实例，以及
then we'll be able to run it and hit the
然后我们就可以运行它并点击
end point from our browser and so this
终点从我们的浏览器等
is all well and good if you want to just
如果你只是想一切都很好
quickly prototype an application we've
快速原型化我们已经拥有的应用程序
seen how you can get rights right into
看到了如何获得权利
it with new technologies and things like
用新技术和类似的东西
this but let's say you'd like to go from
这个，但是假设您想从
implementation to execution if you'd
实施到执行（如果您愿意）
like to deploy this to production
喜欢将其部署到生产中
somewhere and you'll be able to do that
某个地方，您将能够做到这一点
with the docker so if you've heard of
与码头工人联系，所以如果您听说过
docker doctor is a platform for managing
码头医生是一个管理平台
your your builds and allowing you to
您的构建，并允许您
deploy them anywhere in the world
将它们部署在世界任何地方
reproducible fashion so this is this is
可复制的时尚，这就是这个
really easy to do with IntelliJ IDEA 14
使用IntelliJ IDEA 14真的很容易
we've introduced a new plugin for doctor
我们为医生介绍了一个新插件
and with with spring boot this works
与弹簧靴一起工作
just great so you can edit this
太好了，您可以编辑它
configuration and you'll be able to
配置，您将能够
specify
指明
server I set up a docker server already
服务器我已经设置了一个docker服务器
this is a very easy process to do you
这是一个非常简单的过程
can go into your settings and install
可以进入您的设置并安装
docker and give it the docker endpoint
docker并给它docker端点
on your local machine or on a remote
在本地计算机或远程计算机上
instance and you'll need to give it a
实例，您需要给它一个
docker file as well I've set up docker
docker文件以及我已经设置了docker
file inside my working directory here
文件放在我的工作目录中
and what this will do is we'll just take
而这将是我们将采取
this artifact and deploy it to a running
该工件并将其部署到运行中
instance of docker so let's give that a
docker实例，所以我们给它一个
shot right now we'll take a look inside
现在拍摄，我们来看看里面
our run screen here and it looks like
我们的运行屏幕在这里，它看起来像
that this spring application is running
这个春季应用程序正在运行
and it's set up correctly so let's stop
并且设置正确，所以我们停止
this and try this docker deployment so
并尝试此docker部署，以便
the first thing we provide for dr.
我们为博士提供的第一件事
support is an application servers view
支持是应用程序服务器视图
so in docker you have your doctor host
因此，在docker中，您拥有医生主机
and when you're deploying it will be
当您进行部署时
deployed to an image and this image may
部署到映像，此映像可能
have a member of containers that are
有一个容器的成员是
running inside your doctor post and so
在你的医生岗位里面跑等等
you'll be able to view the logs you
您将能够查看您的日志
don't have to connector it through ssh
不必通过ssh连接它
or anything like that you can do it
或类似的事情你可以做到
right inside your application servers
就在您的应用程序服务器内部
you here and there's a log for all of
你在这里，所有的日志
these events so I already have one
这些事件，所以我已经有一个
running container and let's check out
运行容器，让我们签出
the log here now you can view the
现在的日志，您可以查看
processes inside your doctor container
医生容器内的处理
and this should match the running
这应该与跑步
processes if i were to ssh into my
如果我要进入我的进程
doctor instance here and run docker yes
在这里医生实例并运行docker yes
then then i'll get the same information
然后我会得到相同的信息
just inside a nice compact view here and
就在这里一个不错的紧凑视图内
it looks like you'll be able you'll see
看起来您将能够看到
the logs as well so instead of tailing
日志也是如此，而不是拖尾
the log on your command line then you
您的命令行上的日志，然后您
can do it right here this is this
可以在这里做这是这个
the entirety of dr. support right now
整个博士。现在支持
however we do plan on iterating on that
但是我们确实计划对此进行迭代
introducing more support for debugging
引入更多的调试支持
if you need to do debugging you can
如果您需要进行调试，则可以
specify a debugging port in your run
在运行中指定调试端口
configuration and it will give you some
配置，它会给你一些
parameters you can pass in 22 docker
您可以在22个docker中传递的参数
when you run the application okay so so
当您运行应用程序时，可以这样
that's that's two features kind of for
这就是两种功能
going from idea to implementation to
从构想到实施
execution just on a simple spring good
仅仅在一个简单的春季就可以执行
project and so you'll find that this
项目，所以您会发现
features that we provide for a lot of
我们提供的许多功能
these frameworks are kind of
这些框架是
thoughtfully crafted to help you do to
精心设计以帮助您做到
develop your application with as little
少开发应用程序
friction as possible so we kind of try
尽可能的摩擦，所以我们尝试
to anticipate your workflow as you're
预期您的工作流程
going through these events at developing
在开发过程中经历这些事件
your application and and provide these
您的应用程序并提供这些
features and they may not be apparent at
功能，它们可能在以下位置不明显
first but once you're familiar with them
首先，但是一旦您熟悉它们
they'll feel will feel right at home I
他们会觉得自己会在家中
want to switch gears now to talk about
想现在换档谈论
android development and we'll close this
android开发，我们将结束
project and open a new one and so in
项目并打开一个新的，依此类推
android android support i just got a
android android support我刚得到一个
whole lot better with with unit testings
单元测试使整体更好
so this is a kind of a long-awaited
所以这是一种期待已久的
feature for many android developers and
许多Android开发人员的功能，以及
now you can run you're going to test
现在您可以运行要测试
right on the IDE so this is the primary
就在IDE上，所以这是主要的
benefit of using IntelliJ IDEA 14.1 and
使用IntelliJ IDEA 14.1的好处和
now there's a new build variants tool
现在有一个新的构建变体工具
window on your left hand side you'll see
您将看到左侧窗口
the build variants window you can open
您可以打开的构建变体窗口
and close that and if you're running
并关闭它，如果您正在跑步
instrumentation tasks then you know that
检测任务，那么您知道
it has to deploy to the device and
它必须部署到设备上
sometimes that's kind of slow and clunky
有时候有点慢而笨拙
and so if you want to get on board with
所以如果你想加入
TDD test-driven development you want
您想要的TDD测试驱动的开发
these tests run very quickly so i have
这些测试运行非常快，所以我有
my
我的
my instrumentation tests here and this
我的仪器测试在这里和这个
if I deploy this this will run on my
如果我部署这个，它将在我的
device I've connected an Android device
我已连接Android设备的设备
and that that will fellow run and it
那会同路而行
will check these this this message is
将检查这些此消息是
displayed when I click the button
当我单击按钮时显示
however I can do the same thing inside
但是我可以在里面做同样的事情
my IDE by quick switching to the unit
快速切换到本机即可获得我的IDE
testing featuring this is experimental
具有此功能的测试是实验性的
still but you could enable this feature
仍然可以，但是您可以启用此功能
under your settings and you need to be
在您的设置下，您需要
running on the latest version of the
在最新版本的
Android build tools so 1.1 Android
Android构建工具，所以1.1 Android
Gradle plug-in one point 1 point 0 or
Gradle插件1点1点0或
newer and you can just enable unit
较新的，您可以启用该单元
testing support here and then what
在这里测试支持，然后做什么
you'll be able to do is go to your unit
你能做的就是去你的单位
tests and you'll be able to run these
测试，您将能够运行这些
directly so whenever you want to test
直接，因此无论何时您想测试
the method inside your make your main
您内部的方法使您的主要
activity or you're one of the activities
活动或您是其中一项活动
inside your application you can just
在您的应用程序中，您可以
press ctrl shift T and look if you want
按ctrl shift T看看是否
to test this method then you can either
要测试此方法，则可以
choose an existing test class or create
选择现有的测试类别或创建
a new one and that will be created
一个新的，将被创建
inside this test directory fortunate
在这个测试目录里面很幸运
okay so it already contains this test
好吧，所以它已经包含了这个测试
it'll add that that that new test two
它会添加新的测试两个
they're so what I'd like to do right now
他们就是我现在想做的
is I'll run this unit test locally and
我将在本地运行此单元测试，
just to show you that it works so I can
只是向您展示它有效，所以我可以
run this right from where I de and it
从我去的地方开始运行它
will execute it fairly quickly without
将相当快地执行它，而无需
having to go to the device to deploy apk
不得不去设备部署apk
and you can take advantage of the
您可以利用
incremental compliation that's inside
内在的渐进式补充
Android build tools make this fairly
Android构建工具使这一工作变得相当公平
quick
快
let's minimize this while we're waiting
让我们在等待时将其最小化
and I'll show you some other new
我会告诉你一些新的
features in Android so the next feature
Android中的功能，因此下一个功能
that we're introducing and IntelliJ IDEA
我们要介绍的和IntelliJ IDEA
14 is the ability to quickly create
14是快速创建的能力
watch faces with a little template so if
用一个小模板看脸
you select where you can create a new
您选择在哪里可以创建一个新的
watch face template and choose whether
看脸模板并选择是否
analog or digital and that will create a
模拟或数字，这将创建一个
fully functioning watch face inside your
内部功能齐全的表盘
sources so you can use that to
资源，以便您可以使用它来
understand how how watch faces work and
了解表盘如何工作，以及
deploy that directly to advise and
直接部署以建议和
iterate on that kind of customize it and
反复进行这种定制
so forth so this is this is adi template
等等，这是adi模板
that's available for you to use and
供您使用和
there's also a watch face wizard inside
里面还有一个表盘向导
your new project creation so if you
您的新项目创建，因此，如果您
create a new android project then you'll
创建一个新的android项目，然后
be able to give it some watch base light
能够给它一些表底灯
information ok so it looks like our
信息确定，所以看起来像我们的
Gradle build is still refreshing let's
Gradle构建仍然令人耳目一新
check our test to see if they've nice
检查我们的测试，看看它们是否很好
running
跑步
you
您
ok so this test looks like it's still
好的，所以这个测试看起来还是
running but it may have a little
运行，但可能有一点
complete fairly soon and this is all
即将完成，这就是全部
running on site inside my IDE in order
按顺序在我的IDE中的站点上运行
to get this to work you just have to
为了使这个工作，你只需要
remember to add some information to your
记住要向您添加一些信息
build your build.gradle file and these
建立您的build.gradle文件，这些
tests compile dependencies will inform
测试编译依赖项将通知
the IDE informed Gradle that that it
IDE通知Gradle它
will need to import those for the test
将需要导入这些文件进行测试
compile phase and that will happen
编译阶段，那将会发生
directly on 90 we can also test j unit
直接在90上我们也可以测试j单位
here once the Gradle import finishes and
一旦Gradle导入完成，
we'll be able to run these simple tests
我们将能够运行这些简单的测试
that will you give you can even test
你会给你甚至可以测试
that it fails and then implement the
它失败，然后实施
behavior and then tests should succeed
行为，然后测试应该成功
so those are the three features that we
这就是我们的三个特点
want to demonstrate for you today spring
想在春天为您示范
boot with docker and now Android and
使用docker启动，现在使用Android和
Android wear support so there are a
Android Wear支持，因此有一个
number of other frameworks that are
其他框架数量
supported IntelliJ IDEA and we we offer
支持的IntelliJ IDEA，我们提供
support for all of those frameworks in
支持以下所有框架
the same the same manner so we try to
同样的方式，所以我们尝试
look at all the comprehensive features
看所有的综合功能
we can include to make your development
我们可以包括使您的发展
lifecycle a little bit easier and and
生命周期要容易一些，并且
that make up give that to you so this is
弥补给你，所以这是
available in IntelliJ IDEA Community
在IntelliJ IDEA社区中可用
Edition and spring boot is a feature
版本和春季启动是功能
that's available in IntelliJ IDEA
在IntelliJ IDEA中可用
ultimate so I would like to go to
终极的，所以我想去
questions now so if there are any
现在的问题，所以如果有
questions we can feel them right now
问题，我们现在可以感觉到它们
thanks very much
非常感谢
thanks Brendon I really like the fact
谢谢布伦登，我真的很喜欢这个事实
that IntelliJ is now supporting best
IntelliJ现在支持最佳
testing for Android I think that I kind
我为Android测试
of work very vaguely on the periphery of
在外围的工作非常模糊
the year of the Android space and if
Android空间的年份，如果
Stephanie seems to be an area that's
斯蒂芬妮（Stephanie）似乎是
been a bit frustrating for developers
对开发人员来说有点沮丧
yeah it was it was something that took a
是的，这是花了一个
lot of effort to kind of pain and
为减轻痛苦付出了很多努力
consternation didn't have a configure
惊ster没有配置
beforehand I mean if you're running a
事先我的意思是，如果您正在运行
little electric test then you have to do
小电测试，那么你必须做
a lot of configuration inside your build
内部大量配置
script but now there's direct support
脚本，但现在有直接支持
inside the ID which is which is
里面的ID是
fantastic and and when it works it works
棒极了，并且在工作时有效
great there was one question which was
太好了，有一个问题是
specific about your demo which was on
具体关于您的演示
the JSON file with the properties it
具有其属性的JSON文件
said well the question is specifically
说得好，这个问题是专门的
what was that JSON file with the
那个带有
properties it went by too quickly do you
物业过快了吗
know which one I was talking about
知道我在说哪一个
right must be that one
权利一定是那个
I thought I was going deaf but I don't
我以为我要聋了，但我没有
think we can hear Brenda's anymore Oh
认为我们可以再听到布伦达的声音了哦
like oh there we are yeah so so those
就像哦，我们是的，所以那些
those values will be defined inside of
这些值将在内部定义
your edit you're chasing file here and
您的编辑，您正在此处追逐文件，并且
they're kind of automatically validated
它们是自动验证的
as you type so you introduce a new value
键入时会引入一个新值
and and you can just click the Create
然后您只需点击创建
that you can define a configuration key
您可以定义配置密钥
I'll be introduced the properties and
我将介绍属性和
you can go ahead I do something with
你可以继续我做的事
that inside you add another class called
在里面添加另一个类
configuration properties then you'll be
配置属性，那么您将
able to use those values that you said
能够使用您说的那些值
see the other question and the only
看到另一个问题，唯一的
other question I can see is that we
我可以看到的另一个问题是，我们
can't hear you but now we can hear you
听不到您的声音，但现在我们可以听到您的声音了
so oh here we go are there any changes
所以哦，我们走了，那里有什么变化
that relate specifically to grails
特别与grails有关
developments and I don't see anything
事态发展，我什么也没看到
about quails did you I didn't in the
关于鹌鹑，我没有在吗
change list but I know that's something
变更清单，但我知道
that that bring boot is continuing to
那带来引导继续
support and they're there you can learn
支持，他们在那里，您可以学习
more about spring boot and all of this
更多关于弹簧靴以及所有这些
stuff in a webinar that took place
网络研讨会中发生的事情
yesterday in fact and in this webinar
昨天实际上是在这个网络研讨会中
will be available for you to watch today
今天将可供您观看
so i highly recommend that our friend
所以我强烈建议我们的朋友
Stephan nicole will share with you all
斯蒂芬·妮可（Stephan Nicole）将与大家分享
the info latest information about groups
有关组的最新信息
and grails and the development side of
和grails和发展方面
things from from pivotal point so on I
从关键角度出发的事情等等
definitely check that out that that
一定要检查一下
webinar spring into action spring that
网络研讨会变成了行动之春
that's available later today
今天晚些时候可用
great here we go any new updates on the
太棒了，我们在
high DPI you I sport as just mentioned
我刚才提到的高DPI
some text is small and unreadable and
一些文本很小且不可读，
from my point of view i'm using windows
从我的角度来看，我正在使用Windows
on on a HTTP i screen and that has
在HTTP i屏幕上
definitely improved in 14.1 i'm using
我正在使用的14.1绝对有所改善
that's that's kind of well not shown my
那不是我的表现
screen right now so i'm using the new
屏幕现在，所以我正在使用新的
updated version it's definitely better
更新的版本肯定更好
than it was i believe there's probably
比我相信有可能
still some what going on in there it's
还有一些正在发生的事情
definitely an area four and that's
绝对是四个区域，那就是
getting a lot of attention are there any
得到很多关注吗
more questions
更多问题